Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection
1950-1995
Scheuer, Steven H.
4.5 linear ft.
4083309
Biographical History
Steven H. Scheuer is a movie and television historian and critic. He was the editor of Movies on TV (originally titled TV Movie Almanac & Ratings) which went through 17 editions between 1958 and 1993. The first guide of its kind (it preceded the still-active Maltin's TV Movies and Video Guide by ten years), the book contained a mixture of movies, videos and TV movies with ratings up to four stars.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Steven H. Scheuer Publicity Stills Collection consists entirely of still photographs from television shows from the 1950s through the 1990s.
Arrangement of the Collection
Alphabetical by name of person or show.
Related Material
has substantial holdings related to television and broadcasting history. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Radio, television, film; Popular culture; Scheuer, Steven H.; National Broadcasting Company.; Public Broadcasting Service (U.S.); Television -- United States.; Television actors and actresses -- United States.; Television programs.; Popular culture -- United States.; Photographs.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Steven H. Scheuer.
Inventory
- Photographs
  - 20th Century-Fox Hour: A Child of the Regiment, 8/21/1956; 2184; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Preston, Robert; Lee, Candace (Box 1)
  - 20th Century-Fox Hour: Christopher Bean, 6/26/1956; 2462; 8x10, very poor condition; includes caption; Hamilton, Kip; Ritter, Thelma; Hill, Craig (Box 1)
  - 20th Century-Fox Hour: Man on the Ledge, 7/30/1956; 2009; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Miles, Vera; Mitchell, Cameron (Box 1)
  - 77 Sunset Strip: Trouble in the Middle East, 11/11/1960; 2579; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Spencer, Jeff; Byrnes, Edward; Jackson, Sherry (Box 1)
  - A Grand Night: Performing Arts on PTV, 1529; 8x10, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; Mitchell, Leona; PBS Television Network; Ramey, Samuel (Box 1)
  - ABC, 2081; 9x7, fair/average condition (Box 1)
  - ABC Actors: Park, Welk, Thomas, 2359; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Parks, Bert; Welk, Lawrence; Thomas, Danny; Break the bank (Television program); Lawrence Welk Show (television program); Make room for Daddy (Television program) (Box 1)
  - ABC Film Festival Programs: Afternoon Film Festival and Famous Film Festival, 2537; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Edwards, Allyn (Box 1)
  - ABC Radio, 2079; 8x10, fair/average condition; Schwartz; Neil (Box 1)
  - ABC Radio Programs: George Jessel Salutes and American Music Hall, 12/7/1953; 2586; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Harmer, Shirley; Jessel, George (Box 1)
  - ABC Television Programs: Day in Court and The Untouchables: Mexican Stakeout, 2334; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Repp, Stafford; Lewis, Elisabeth (Box 1)
  - Adventure, 5/16/1988; 1500; 10x8, excellent condition; Swan, Robert; Antarctica; PBS Television Network (Box 1)
  - Adventures in Paradise: Big Sur, 1943; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; McKay, Gardner; von Furstenburg, Betsy (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: Ricky's Big Night, 2487; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Pope DuPont, Elaine; Nelson, Rick (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: The Closed Circuit, 3/26/1954; 2491; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Nelson, Ozzie; Edwards, Penny (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Ozzie and Harriet: The International Set, 5/28/1958; 2493; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Garris, Joan; Nelson, David; Burgess, Jane (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Robin Hood: The Haunted Mill, 2621; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Gauge, Alexander; Grenne, Richard; O'Farrel1, Bernadette (Box 1)
  - Adventures of Sir Lancelot, 2409; 7x9, poor condition; Russell, William (Box 1)
  - Alaskans Contest at Gold Bottom, 11/15/1960; 2255; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Provine, Dorothy; Moore, Roger (Box 1)
  - Alaskans: Doc Booker, 12/6/1959; 2338; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Tiny Tiger (Long-haired chihuahua); Provine, Dorothy (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Hour: The Big Wave, 9/30/1956; 2230; 10x8, very poor condition; includes caption; Cronyn, Hume (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Premiere: A Place to Hide, 2513; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Stockwell, Dean; Hackett, Joan (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Presents: House of the Dead, 6/7/1960; 2428; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Raki, Laya (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Presents: Reunion, 11/24/1959; 2632; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Furstenberg, Betsy Von (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Presents: The Lonely Room, 5/31/1959; 2171; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Noverese, Letizia; Mioni, Fabrizio (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Presents: The Navigator, 7/21/1959; 2523; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Ellenstein, Robert; Dubbins, Don (Box 1)
  - Alcoa Theatre: The Days of November, 2278; 8x10, very poor condition; includes caption; Lemmon, Jack; Williams, Adam (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents, 8/8/1955; 1999; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hitchcock, Alfred (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents, 10/3/1956; 2003; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Cronyn, Hume; Gleason, James (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Arthur, 6/27/1960; 2603; 10x8, good condition; includes caption; Harvey, Laurence; Court, Hazel (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Day of the Bullet, 6/l6/1960; 2649; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Gordon, Barry; Patrick, Dennis (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Escape to Sonoita, 6/20/1960; 2270; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; depicts Hitchcock talking to actors not seen in image; Hitchcock, Alfred (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Hooked, 9/7/1960; 2286; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Francis, Anne (Box 1)
  - Alfred Hitchcock Presents: Place of Shadows, 2/9/1956; 2269; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Damon, Mark; Sloane, Everett; Stevens, Robert (Box 1)
  - AM Radio Sales Company, 2077; 8x10, good condition (Box 1)
  - American Playhouse, 1513; 8x10, excellent condition; 3 photographs on sheet: Journey Toward Genius, Suspicion, and Strange Interlude; Modine, Matthew; Andrews, Anthony; Curtin, Jane; Jackson, Glenda; Petherbridge, Edward; Dukes, David; Howard, Ken; PBS Television Network (Box 1)
  - An Ocean Apart, 1495; 7x5, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain; Reagan, Ronald (Box 1)
  - Andy Williams Show, 12/27/1963; 2648; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Williams, Andy (Box 1)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, 1977; 9x6, extremely poor condition; includes caption; 3 photographs on sheet; Martin, Mary (Box 1)
  - Annie Get Your Gun, 1983; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Martin Mary (Box 1)
  - Annie Oakley, 2446; 8x10, very poor condition; Davis, Gail (Box 1)
  - Annie Oakley, 2542; 4x5, good condition; Hawkins, Jimmy; Davis, Gail (Box 1)
  - Anybody Can Play (Game show), 2283; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Fenneman, Clifford; Fenneman, George (Box 1)
  - Arlene Francis Show, 2201; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Gabel, Peter (Box 1)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre: A Baby Named X, 4/3/1956; 2488; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Overton, Frank; Osterwald, Bibi (Box 1)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre: Strange War of Sergeant Krenzer, 2375; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Kiley, Richard; Obregon, Antonio; Palmer, Betsy (Box 1)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre: The Bystander, 2181; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; East Berlin (East Germany); Prince, William; McKay, Peggy; Communism (Box 1)
  - Armstrong Circle Theatre: Twelve Cases of Murder, 6/25/1958; 2425; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Oakland, Simon; Marth, Frank (Box 1)
  - Art Linkletter Show, 2264; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Linkletter, Art; Farrell, Sharon (Box 1)
  - Austin City Limits, 1/6/1988; 1520; 8x10, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; O'Hara, Jamie; PBS Television Network; Kane, Kiernan; O'Kanes (Musical group); Cash, Rosanne (Box 1)
  - Austin City Limits, 1/16/1988; 1525; 8x10, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; Asleep at the Wheel (Musical group); PBS Television Network; Benson, Ray; Forester Sisters (Musical group) (Box 1)
  - Bacall on Bogart, March 1988; 1486; 5x7, excellent condition; Bogart, Humphrey; PBS Television Network (Box 1)
  - Bachelor Father, 2342; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Corcoran, Noreen; Jasper (Dog); Tong, Sammee (Box 1)
  - Banducci, Enrico, 2732; 8x10, fair/average condition (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 2/1/1963; 2209; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Price, Leontyne; Opera (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 9/30/1960; 2274; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Howes, Sally Ann; Cliburn, Van; Goodman, Benny; Voorhees, Donald (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 3/20/1959; 2297; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; artist’s rendering of performers on the show; Iturbi, Jose; Clooney, Rosemary; Ferrer, Jose; MacKenzie, Gisele; Voorhees, Donald; Gedda, Nicolai; Tozzi, Giorgio; Eglevsky, Andre; Tallchief, Maria (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 4/9/1959; 2298; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Ferrer, Jose; Iturbi, Jose (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 10/26/1962; 2426; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Tadlock, Tad; Rall, Tommy; West Point Glee Club; Wright, Martha; Johannesen, Grant (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour, 2630; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Galloway, David; Nelson, Gene (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour: A Trip to Christmas, 1934; 10x8; includes caption; Raitt, John; Morgan, Jane (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour: Girl of the Golden West, 2197; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Munsel, Patrice; Sullivan, Brian; Opera (Box 1)
  - Bell Telephone Hour: The Mikado, 1961; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Marx, Groucho (Box 1)
  - Ben Casey: A Few Brief Lines for Dave, 11/13/1961; 2300; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Jaffe, Sam; Ackerman, Bettye (Box 1)
  - Ben Casey: Allie, 9/25/1963; 2540; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Cooley, Isabelle (Box 1)
  - Bennetts, 2598; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Houston, Paula; Gibson, Don (Box 1)
  - Big Town, 1974; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Wilson, Steve (Box 1)
  - Bing Crosby Show, 9/15/1958; 2172; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Crosby, Bing; Martin, Dean (Box 1)
  - Bing Crosby Show, 2457; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Lawrence, Carol (Box 1)
  - Bob Cummings Show, 2455; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Cummings, Bob; Snowden, Leigh; DeCamp, Rosemary (Box 1)
  - Bob Cummings Show: Bob Gets Harvey a Raise, 2/14/1958; 2193; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Lansing, Joi; Cummings, Bob; Gaye, Lisa (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Buick Show, 2268; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Keel, Howard; Roberta (television musical); Hope, Bob; Alberghetti, Anna Maria (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Buick Show, 2592; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hope, Bob; Keel, Howard; Alberghetti, Anna Maria (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Buick Show, 11/13/1959; 2644; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hope, Bob Paige, Janis (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Buick Show: Bunions to Billions skit, 4/21/1961; 2399; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Hope, Bob (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Chevy Show, 4/7/1957; 2385; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Paige, Janis (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre: Seven Miles of Bad Road, 8/2/1963; 2422; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Parker, Eleanor; Hunter, Jeffrey; Hope, Bob; Temple Houston (Television program) (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Presents the Chrysler Theatre: The Shattered Glass, 11/13/1964; 2442; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; O'Herlihy, Dan; Jones, Shirley (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Show, 5/20/1954; 2257; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Maxwell, Marilyn; Hope, Bob (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Show, 2303; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Fleming, Rhonda; Hope, Bob (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Television Show, 10/7/1953; 2176; 8x9.5, fair/average condition; includes caption; Harris, Phil (Box 1)
  - Bob Hope Television Show, 10/30/1953; 2420; 8x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Roberta (Musical); MacMurray, Fred; Hope, Bob (Box 1)
  - Bodywatch, 1/23/1988; 1499; 8x10, excellent condition; Zigy Kaluzny, photographer; Duke, James H. "Red" Jr.; PBS Television Network (Box 1)
  - Bold Journey: Journey to Lapland, 7/12/1956; 2655; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Parker, Ejordis Kittel; Scandinavia -- Description and travel (Box 1)
  - Bonanza: The Actress, 2/1/1963; 2381; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Crowley, Patricia (Box 2)
  - Bonanza: The Way Station, 6/16/1963; 2273; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Vaughn, Robert; Wells, Dawn (Box 2)
  - Boris Godunov, 3/3/1961; 1991; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Tozzi, Giorgio (Box 2)
  - Bourbon Street Beat, 7/4/1959; 2604; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Howell, Arlene (Box 2)
  - Bourbon Street Beat: Portrait of Lenore, 7/25/1960; 2727; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Howell, Arlene (Box 2)
  - Bourbon Street Beat: The Mourning Cloak, 10/12/1959; 2605; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Howell, Arlene; Long, Richard (Box 2)
  - Bourbon Street Beat: The Taste of Ashes, 10/5/1959; 2599; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Howell, Arlene (Box 2)
  - Breakfast Club, 2500; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; McNeill, Don; Allison, Fran; Richards, Carol; Cowling, Sam; Noel, Dick (Box 2)
  - Breaking Point: A Land More Cruel, 2322; 7x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Parker, Eleanor (Box 2)
  - Breck Sunday Showcase: Turn the Key Deftly, 2440; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Harris, Julie; Schell, Maximilian (Box 2)
  - Breck Sunday Showcase: Turn the Key Deftly, 2/12/1960; 2608; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Harris, Julie (Box 2)
  - Breckir, Patricia, 2480; 8x10, poor condition (Box 2)
  - Brennan, Walter, 2372; 7x9, good condition; Gobel, George (Box 2)
  - Bronco, 2221; 7.5x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hardin, Ty (Box 2)
  - Bronco: A Sure Thing, 1/22/1962; 2731; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Hardin, Ty (Box 2)
  - Bronco: Bodyguard, 10/20/1959; 2473; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Hardin, Ty (Box 2)
  - Bronco: The Besieged, 9/23/1958; 2620; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hardin, Ty; Granville, Joan (Box 2)
  - Bronco: The Devil's Spawn, 2574; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Hardin, Ty (Box 2)
  - Buddy Holly and the Crickets: A Tribute, March 1988; 1476; 10x8, good condition; William Griggs, photographer; Holly, Buddy; Allison, Jerry; Fundraisers; Maudlin, Joe; PBS Television Network (Box 2)
  - Buddy Holly and the Crickets: A Tribute, 1478; 10x8, excellent condition; William Griggs, photographer; 2 images on sheet; PBS Television Network; Fundraisers; Jennings, Waylon; Holly, Buddy (Box 2)
  - Burke's Law: Who Killed Mr. X?, 9/27/1963; 2460; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Harding, Ann (Box 2)
  - Caesar Presents, 6/22/1955; 2521; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Nichols, Barbara (Box 2)
  - Caesar's Hour, 5/25/1955; 2577; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Caesar, Sid; Caesar, Michele; Caesar, Richard; Television Father of the Year (Box 2)
  - Californians, 9/25/1957; 1958; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Fields, Darlene (Box 2)
  - Californians, 10/1/1957; 2629; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Leslie, Nan (Box 2)
  - Canadian Football, 8/3/1954; 2386; 9x7, very poor condition; includes caption; Walker, Douglas (Peahead); Ottawa Rough Riders (Football team); Crowe, Clem; Montreal Alouettes (Football team); Canadian Football League (CFL) (Box 2)
  - Candid Camera, 9/6/1960; 2004; 10x8, good condition; includes caption; Funt, Allen (Box 2)
  - Cavalcade of America: Young Andy Jackson, 8/24/1954; 2623; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Lindgren, Orley; Gray, Billy; Hale, Fiona (Box 2)
  - CBS Television Studio Plant, 2036; 7x9, good condition; includes caption, illustration rendered as an artists' sketch (Box 2)
  - CBS Television Studio Plant, 2037; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; illustration rendered as an artists' sketch (Box 2)
  - Center Stage: The Heart of a Clown, 2366; 13x14, poor condition; includes caption; Nichols, Barbara (Box 2)
  - Charisse, Cyd (aka Tula Ellice Finklea), 2636; 8x10, very poor condition; Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (MGM) (Box 2)
  - Charisse, Cyd (aka Tula Ellice Finklea), 2637; 8x10, very poor condition; Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer (MGM) (Box 2)
  - Chet Huntley Reporting for Mutual of Omaha, 12/22/1961; 2445; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Huntley, Chet; News (Box 2)
  - Cheyenne, 2454; 8x10, poor condition; includes caption; Walker, Clint (Box 2)
  - Cheyenne: Lone Patrol, 8/21/1961; 2522; 7.5x9, very poor condition; includes caption; Walker, Clint (Box 2)
  - Cheyenne: Standoff, 5/6/1958; 2640; 7x9, poor condition; includes caption; Page, Joy (Box 2)
  - Cheyenne: The Traveler, 1/3/1956; 2373; 8x10, very poor condition; includes caption; Hopper, Dennis; Armstrong, Robert; Gleason, James; Brewster, Diane; Walker, Clint; Ankrum, Morris (Box 2)
  - Chrysler Presents a Bob Hope special, 9/6/1963; 2414; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Stone, Butch; Brown, Stumpy; Martin, Dean; Hope, Bob (Box 2)
  - Climax: A Matter of Life and Death, 11/21/1957; 2729; 8x10, good condition; Palmer, Betsy (Box 2)
  - Climax: Carnival at Midnight, 2010; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Paget, Debra (Box 2)
  - Climax: Shower of Stars, 2339; 7x9, fair/average condition; Costa, Mary (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Great World of Timothy Colt, 3/27/1958; 2261; 8x10, good condition; Hayes, Maggie (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Hand of Evil, 5/10/1957; 2007; 8x10, good condition; Miles, Vera (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Hand of Evil, 7/30/1956; 2008; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Miles, Vera; Forsythe, John (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Long Count, 2353; 8x10, fair/average condition; Lindfors, Viveca (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Midas Touch, 2398; 8x10, fair/average condition; Hayes, Margaret (Box 2)
  - Climax: The Pink Cloud, 2206; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; Forrest, Sally (Box 2)
  - Coke Time: Starring Eddie Fisher, 2228; 8x10, good condition; includes caption; King, Peggy; Fisher, Eddie (Box 2)
  - Coke Time: Starring Eddie Fisher, 10/8/1954; 2337; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Fisher, Eddie; Weaver, Sylvester L, Jr.; Sacks, Emanuel (Box 2)
  - Collectors, 4/2/1988; 1519; 10x8, excellent condition; Greg Anderson, photographer; 2 photographs on sheet; Rau, Bob; Garrett, Dana; Circus; Circus World Museum (Wis); PBS Television Network; Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey Combined Shows (Box 2)
  - Collins, 2098; 8x10, fair/average condition; Collins addressing conventioneers (Box 2)
  - Colt .45: Gallows at Granite Gap, 11/8/1957; 2407; 8xl0, poor condition; Preston, Wayde (Box 2)
  - Colt .45: Rare Specimen, 2182; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Preston, Wayde (Box 2)
  - Colt .45: Small Man, 10/17/1957; 2223; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption (Box 2)
  - Confession, 1994; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Koelling, Donald; Wyatt, Jack (Box 2)
  - Conflict: Girl on a Subway, 1/18/1957; 2466; 8x10, poor condition; Caption on back; Hamilton, Barry; Garner, Sam; Wood, Natalie (Box 2)
  - Conflict: Silent Journey, 12/25/1956; 2612; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Haynes, Roberta (Box 2)
  - Conflict: The People Against McQuade, 1973; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Crayne, Dani (Box 2)
  - Connor, Nadine, 2734; 8x10, poor condition (Box 2)
  - Conserving America: Wetlands, 1/11/1988; 1491; 5x8, excellent condition; Everglades (Fla.); Douglas, Marjory Stoneman (Box 2)
  - Constant Husband, 10/5/1955; 2248; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Kendall, Kay; Harrison, Rex; French, Valerie; Adams, Jill; Howells, Ursula; Maurey, Nicole; Dumville, Roma (Box 2)
  - Convention Coverage, 2554; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Wood, Barry; McElrath, George; Taylor, Davidson; McAndrew, William R. (Box 2)
  - Conversation with Herbert Hoover, 10/9/1955; 2412; 9x7, fair/average condition; includes caption; Hoover, Herbert (Box 2)
  - Cooper, Sally, 2490; 5x7, poor condition (Box 2)
  - Country Music Crossroads, March 1988; 1479; 8x10, excellent condition; PBS Television Network; Fundraisers; Oak Ridge Boys (Musical group); Osmond, Marie (Box 2)
  - Country Music Crossroads, 1530; 10x8, excellent condition; 2 photographs on sheet; Travis, Randy; Newton, Juice; PBS Television Network (Box 2)
  - Court-Martial of Billy Cooper, 1932; 8xl0, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Cooper, Gary (Box 2)
  - Crossroads: St. George and the Dragon, 1/27/1956; 2383; 8x10; includes caption; Landon, Michael; Arlen, Richard (Box 2)
  - Danny Thomas Show, 9/11/1967; 2625; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Thomas, Danny; Hagen, Jean (Box 3)
  - Dante, 8/1/1960; 2616; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Dante's Inferno; Peterson, Nan; Duff, Howard (Box 3)
  - Dateline Disneyland, 1970; 8x10, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Dunne, Irene (Box 3)
  - Dateline Disneyland, 7/17/1955; 2281; 10x8, fair/average condition; includes caption; depicts launching of the "Mark Twain," a Western paddle steamer (Box 3)
  - Dave Garroway Show, 5/7/1954; 2244; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Harmer, Shirley (Box 3)
  - David Brinkley's Journal, 4/12/1963; 2377; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Haiti; Brinkley, David (Box 3)
  - David Niven Show, 1989; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Mitchell, Cameron; Lester, Vonne (Box 3)
  - Death Valley Days: Gold is Where You Find It, 1933; 9.5x7.5, extremely poor condition; includes caption; Mather, George (Box 3)
  - Death Valley Days: I Am Joaquin, 1963; 9x7, good condition; includes caption; Cooper, Jeanne; Damler, John (Box 3)
  - Degrassi Jr. High, 1/5/1988; 1496; 10x8, excellent condition; PBS Television Network (Box 3)
  - Deputy, 2433; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Fonda, Henry; Case, Allen (Box 2)
  - Deputy: The Two Faces of Bob Claxton, 2/27/1960; 2588; 7x9, good condition; includes caption; Keim, Betty Lou; Montgomery, Robert, Jr. (Box 3)
  - Dick Powell Show: A Time to Die, 1/9/1962; 2267; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Powell, Pamela; Powell, Dick (Box 3)
  - Dick Powell Show: Ricochet, 10/3/1961; 2451; 7x9, fair/average condition; includes caption; Heflin, Van (Box 3)
  - Digges, 4/8/1964; 2092; 7x9, fair/average condition (Box 3)
  - Dinah Shore Show: A Girl, A Boy, A Piano, 3/26/1963; 2651; 9x7, poor condition; includes caption; Darin, Bobby; Shore, Dinah (Box 3)
  - Discoveries Underwater, 3/21/1988; 1517; 8x10, excellent condition; Russell England, photographer; 2 photographs on sheet; PBS Television Network; Admiral Gardner (Ship); Mediterranean Sea -- Description and Travel (Box 3)
  - Disneyland, 2118; 9x7, fair/average condition (Box 3)
  - Disneyland, 2316; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption (Box 3)
  - Disneyland: Adventures of Mickey Mouse, 10/12/1955; 2478; 8x10, fair/average condition; includes caption; Goofy (Fictitious character); Donald Duck (Fictitious character); Mickey Mouse (Fictitious character) (Box 3)